听力录音材料第一节：听句子，选择与所听内容或语境相关的信息。每个句子读两遍。
I'll buy some flowers for my teacher.
2. What a happy girl she is!
3. There is nothing in the bottle.
4. I usually take a bus to school.
5. My brother enjoys reading books.
brother enjoys reading books.
第二节：听句子，选择恰当的应答语。每个句子读两遍。
Which color do you like better, red or purple?
7. I got an A in the P.E.
test. 8. What does your cousin do?
9. Would you please show me the way to the restroom?
10. How do you like the movie?
第三节：听对话及问题，选择能回答所提问题的最佳答案。每段对话读两遍。
How do you It's 4.20.
Question What time is it now?
12. Peter, where have you been these days?
I've been volunteering in a hospital recently.
Question Where has Peter been volunteering these days?
13. Tony, who is the lovely girl with long black hair?
Oh, she is my younger sister.
Question What does Tony's sister look like?
14. Who is the lovely girl with long black hair?
Oh, she is my younger sister.
What does Tony's sister look like?
14. Sam, has your English teacher Linda come back yet?
Not yet. She will be back from teacher's training in two weeks.
Question How soon will Linda come back?
Sam, has your English teacher Linda come back yet?
Not yet. She will be back from teacher's training in two weeks.
Question How soon will Linda come back?
15. I'm a little nervous about the party.
I don't know most of the guests.
Don't worry, Diana.
I'll introduce you to them.
Question Why is Diana nervous about the party?
第四节，听短文，根据其内容选出能回答下列问题的。的最佳答案，短文读两遍。
nervous Hello, everyone.
Welcome to today's Cooking Husbands.
Can husbands do well in the kitchen, too?
Of course we can.
Today's special for our lovely husbands is a soup.
Before we start, get the following ready.
4 carrots, half cabbage, half a bottle tomato sauce, and half a kilo of beef.
First, cut the materials in pieces.
Next, put them all in the pot and cook for about 20 minutes.
Then, put in the tomato sauce and cook for another 10 minutes.
Finally, add a teaspoon of salt before you turn off the gas.
Have a taste of this lovely soup.
This can be the most delicious home cooking you have ever done.
Welcome to today's Cooking Husbands.
Can husbands do well in the kitchen, too?
Of course we can.
Today's special for our lovely husbands is a soup.
Before we start, get the following ready.
4 carrots, half cabbage, half a bottle tomato sauce, and half a kilo of beef.
First, cut the materials in pieces.
Next, put them all in the pot and cook for about 20 minutes.
Then, put in the tomato sauce and cook for another 10 minutes.
Finally, add a teaspoon of salt before you turn off the gas.
Have a taste of this lovely soup.
This can be the most delicious home cooking you have ever done.
Thank